the the migraine thing. Can you explain
just that whole process and then how you
were able to get yourself in a place to
play football again?
>> Uh so um that came about last year um
going into the season a little bit. It
started to come back in the middle of
the season. Um I got a treatment on it
and and uh everything everything is good
now. So
>> Jake, [snorts]
>> hey W. Um you've it looks like you've
been used in quite a few different
spots. free safety in the box nickel
>> is do you have like any understanding of
how Lou Andrew wants to use you in this
system?
>> Um uh I'm not 100% on that but but uh as
of our talks and stuff um I'm going to
be moved around a bit but um uh 100% in
one spot I'm not sure on that though.
>> Do you prefer it that way being kind of
a chess piece?
>> Yep. Yep. Uh I've I've I've been moved
around in different spots my whole
career. I didn't play corner. I didn't
play nickel. I didn't play free. I
didn't play strong. So,
>> thanks
>> Chap.
>> Yeah. Wa. Again, young players still
developing, I guess, is the way you look
at yourself. What do you bring? What
what traits do you think you bring that
make you a a viable uh you know, player?
>> Uh I play fast. Uh I can play different
spots and uh and I'm very very smart. Um
uh once I have a read on something, I
just go. So,
>> um I know a few members just joined. Um
so, if we have any other questions, if
not, we will wrap it up. Uh Joel, go
ahead.
>> Uh I'm sorry I got on a little bit late.
I might I might have missed uh the a
question about with the It was a nerve
issue leading to the migraines last
year.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Um and I guess that's that's taken care
of now.
>> Yes.
Um what what was the difficulty of going
through that just kind of when you were
hitting your stride and getting to play
defense?
>> Um honestly it was uh it was a really
tough on me but uh I um I literally
serve a God that uh doesn't make no
mistakes in my life. So um that was
honestly I would say it's a blessing in
disguise because it really sat me down
and then made me realize how life is
like very very precious. So, um, just
going through it, it was it was tough,
but, you know, I, um, I lean on God. So,
and then, you know, I'm here now. So,
>> was it always something that you that
you knew was going to be, uh, able to be
repaired, fixed, you know, get get
healthier, or
>> Yeah. Um, I knew it was always a
treatment to help help it, but, in the
moment, you feel so lost. But, uh, as of
getting the treatment, um, it, uh, it'll
put a smile on my face and, um, you
know, I'm great now.
We'll go back to Jake. Uh
>> yeah, just wanted to kind of get your
gauge on what the process of for free
agency was like for you. I I know there
was some real optimism uh with the
Cowboys. I I just
>> from our point of view looking at it
looks like a lot of people were kind of
bummed to lose you and that didn't work
out.
>> Did you like how much did you test the
market and then I guess what led you to
Indie?
>> Um you know I had quite I had quite a
few teams. um talking with my agent, I'm
not going to really get into the teams
and stuff, but uh you know uh I can
speak back on the team that I was with.
You know, it um it um it actually came
down to it to where you know, obviously
they did want me back, but uh it was a
decision for me to make to go and just
spread my uh wings and then just but but
like far the whole process of it though,
um I didn't really think too much on it.
I didn't let it stress me out because I
was already stressed out enough during
the season, you know, sitting out. So,
um, you know, I picked up golf and and I
started golfing to to like to like to
like take my mind off of it. So, um, the
process was pretty smooth for me. Uh, I
never let myself get too high. I never
let myself get too low. I really stayed
like neutral. So, um, the process was
great though
>> James.
>> Got to find you a course out here, man.
Excited about that.
>> Definitely.
>> Um, just looking at your overall journey
though, trying to miss these moments
with guys. I mean, you get another
contract in the NFL. It's a hard league.
You were undrafted. So, did you have a
moment to maybe just reflect and
appreciate how far you've come even
after the season you had last year?
>> Man, um after the season was over with,
um you really don't know, especially uh
me signing a win with Dallas last year
and then the season's over and I sat
out. Um it really made me appreciate my
time with them. Um and uh being in being
in the league for four years, uh
especially for especially for an
undrafted guy, bro, it it's like it's
like you like it's hard to make it past
year three and and uh I'm going into
year five now. So, um it's a blessing,
man. And and and I wouldn't switch this
journey for anything else.
Nathan,
>> uh, before, um, some of the the nerve
issues cropped up last year as you were
taking on a bigger role on that defense,
getting some starts, what did you feel
like opened up that opportunity? Um, and
and what parts of your game did you feel
like you maybe took some big leaps over
the past offseason to work into the
lineup and be a more frequent
contributor? Um, so to speak on like my
traits that that that I think I got
better at, um, I would I would really
say being being a real quarterback on
the back end of the defense. Um, um, I'm
a talker. I talk a lot. Even if even if
you don't get what I'm saying, like like
I'mma talk to you. I'm I'mma tell you
where where where I'm going. I'mma tell
you where you need to go. Um, and that's
something I took pride in on uh, getting
better at, especially helping me get
more playing playing time. And then as I
started playing, the game the game
slowed down for me. Like like if like
you literally know what you're doing,
the game slows down. And then those
three games that I started last last
year against the Panthers, the
Cardinals, and uh the Jets, um they felt
great like like I wasn't thinking, I was
just playing. So um that really helped
my my game to when I had to start last
year. And when when you um you know as
you maybe had a chance to familiarize
yourself with the you know the Colts
defense, the coaching staff, kind of
maybe how they how they view you in this
system. How do you feel like um you guys
can can create a good match there
between you joining this unit?
>> Um like I said, I'm a player that plays
fast. I'm smart and physical. Um and uh
I think I think that like Coach Lou
loves those guys. So, um, and I think we
are going to mesh well. I'm not gonna
really get into, you know what I'm
saying, like the, uh, plays the style of
defense that we, uh, run here, but, uh,
I think I think and I know we are going
to me mesh really, really well.
>> Awesome. Thanks.